<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="RoQME_Features"
      label="RoQME Eclipse Tools"
      version="1.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="University of Extremadura, University of Málaga, Biometric Vox S.L.">

   <description url="https://robmosys.eu/roqme/">
      RoQME Plugins. &quot;RoQME: Dealing with non-functional properties through global Robot Quality-of-Service Metrics&quot; was an Integrated Technical Project (ITP) funded in the context of the EU H2020 RobMoSys project. RoQME provides software engineers with methods and tools to deal with system-level non-functional properties, enabling the specification of global Quality-of-Service (QoS) metrics in robotics.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      RoQME is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published
by the Free Software Foundation; either version 3 of the License,
or any later version.
RoQME is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY
or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public
License for more details.
GNU GPLv3 link: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html
Copyright (C) 2019  University of Extremadura, University of
Malaga, Biometric Vox S.L.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      RoQME is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or any later version.

RoQME is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.

GNU GPLv3 link: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html

Copyright (C) 2019  University of Extremadura, University of Malaga, Biometric Vox S.L.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.editor.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.editor.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.generator"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.mapping.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.mapping.editor.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.mapping.editor.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.metamodel"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="roqme.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
